x-block.io 2019-04-01

# 

                                             PRIVACY POLICY
About this Privacy Policy
1.       This is the Privacy Policy for X-Block Foundation Ltd. (“X-Block”). In this Privacy Policy, “we”,
“us” or “our” refers to X-Block.
General
2.       We will only use your personal data where you have given us your consent and in the manner
         set out in this Privacy Policy.
3.       This Privacy Policy sets out the manner in which we collect, use, disclose and process your
         personal data when you:
         3.1.     access or use our website and mobile applications (“Applications”) and services;
                  and/or
         3.2.     provide us with your personal data, regardless of the medium through which such
                  personal data is provided.
4.       By providing us with your personal data, you consent to our collection, use, disclosure
         (including transfer) and processing of your personal data in accordance with this Privacy
         Policy. Please D O N O T provide any personal data to us if you do not accept this Privacy
         Policy.
Amendments to this Privacy Policy
5.       We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time without notice to you. The updated
         Privacy Policy will supersede earlier versions and will apply to personal data provided to us
         previously. The updated Privacy Policy will be made available upon request from us and on
         our Applications. If you do not accept any amendment to the Privacy Policy, please contact
         our Data Protection Officer (see paragraph 26 below).
How do we collect information?
6.       What is personal data. “Personal data” is data that can be used to identify a natural person.
7.       We collect personal data that is relevant to our business relationship with you. We may collect
         your personal data directly or indirectly through various channels, such as when:
         7.1.     you provide us with your personal data for whatever reasons;
         7.2.     you authorise us to obtain your personal data from a third party;
         7.3.     you register your interest for the purpose of being whitelisted as a potential acquirer
                  of the tokens we offer for sale;
         7.4.     you register for a user account on our Applications;
         7.5.     you use our Applications and services;
         7.6.     you contact us or interact with our employees through various communication
                  channels, for example, through social media platforms, messenger platforms such as
                  Telegram, face-to-face meetings, telephone calls, emails, fax and letters;
         7.7.     you transact with us, contact us or request that we contact you;
         7.8.     you request to be included in an email or our mailing list;
         7.9.     your images are captured via CCTV cameras while you are within our premises;
         7.10.    your images are captured via photographs or videos taken b y us or our
                  representatives when you attend events organised by us; and/or
         7.11.    you submit an employment application or when you provide documents or information
                  including your resume in connection with any employment application.
8.       Our Applications may contain certain technologies that collects data in the manner described
         in this Privacy Policy (see paragraph 25 below) or the applicable terms and conditions.
                                   Privacy Policy || X-Block Foundation Ltd.

9.    Voluntary provision of personal data. Your provision of personal data to us is voluntary
      and you may withdraw your consent for us to use your personal data at any time. However, if
      you choose not to provide us with the personal data we require, it may not be possible for us
      to contact you, or provide products or services which you need from us.
10.   Providing personal data belonging to others. In certain circumstances, you may also
      provide us with personal data of persons other than yourself. If you do so, you warrant that
      you have informed him/her of the purposes for which we are collecting his/her personal data
      and that he/she has consented to your disclosure of his/her personal data to us for those
      purposes. You agree to indemnify and hold us harmless from and against any and all claims
      by such individuals relating to our collection, use and disclosure of such personal data in
      accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.
11.   Accuracy and completeness of personal data. You are responsible for ensuring that all
      personal data that you provide to us is true, accurate and complete. You are responsible for
      informing us of any changes to your personal data.
How do we use your information?
12.   Generally, w e collect, use or disclose your personal data for one or more of the following
      purposes:
      12.1.    provide you with products and/or services that you request for;
      12.2.    managing your relationship with us;
      12.3.    facilitating your use of our Applications;
      12.4.    to resolve any disputes, investigating any complaint, claim or dispute or any actual or
               suspected illegal or unlawful conduct;
      12.5.    assisting you with your enquiries, and to respond to your feedback, complaints and
               requests;
      12.6.    to notify you of our products, services, programs and events;
      12.7.    to process your job application and assess your suitability for the position applied for;
      12.8.    to manage the safety and security of our premises and event premises (including but
               not limited to carrying out CCTV surveillance and conducting security clearances);
               and/or
      12.9.    any other reasonable purposes related to the aforesaid.
13.   Business p u r p o s e s .  We m a y also use your personal data for purposes connected or
      relevant to our business, such as:
      13.1.    complying with our legal obligations and requirements;
      13.2.    complying with international sanctions and applicable regulation for securities and to
               counter money-laundering or financing of terrorism;
      13.3.    enforcing obligations owed to us, and contractual terms and conditions;
      13.4.    carrying out market expansion plans, research, data analysis, testing, research,
               statistical and survey purposes;
      13.5.    staff training; and/or
      13.6.    any other reasonable purposes related to the aforesaid.
14.   Marketing. If you have consented, w e may use your personal data, from time to time, for
      additional purposes such as to inform you of our products, services, programs and events,
      and to inform you of the latest activities, special offers and promotions offered by our strategic
      business partners and associates.
How do we protect your personal data?
15.   We will take reasonable precautions to safeguard your personal data.
16.   While reasonable precautions will be taken to ensure that the information you provide is
      protected against unauthorized o r unintended access, w e cannot be held responsible for
                                 Privacy Policy || X-Block Foundation Ltd.

       unauthorized or unintended access that is beyond our control, such as hacking or
       cybercrimes.
How long do we retain your personal data for?
17.    We will keep your personal data for so long as we need the personal data for our business
       and legal purposes.
Third Party Disclosure
18.    We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personal data to third parties without your
       consent.
19.    Consent for disclosure to third parties. If you have consented to our disclosure of your
       personal data to our strategic business partners and associates, w e m a y disclose your
       personal data to them. They will use your personal data only for the purposes you have
       consented to.
20.    Disclosure to service providers. You agree that w e may disclose or share your personal
       data with third parties such as:
       20.1.    service providers and data processors working on our behalf and providing services
                to us such as conducting know-your-clients checks, accounting, data processing or
                management services, website hosting, maintenance and operation services, e-mail
                message services, analysis services, h andling of payment transactions, marketing
                etc; and
       20.2.    our consultants and professional advisors (such as accountants, lawyers, auditors).
21.    We m a y also disclose your personal data as required or permitted b y law, including to
       regulatory authorities, statutory bodies, public agencies or law enforcement, or to enforce our
       site policies or protect our or others’ rights, property or safety.
Transfer of personal data to another country
22.    You fully understand and unambiguously consent that we may transfer your personal data to
       any country for the purposes set out above.
23.    Protection of your personal data. If we transfer your personal data to another country or
       territory, we will ensure that the recipient of the personal data protects your personal data to
       the same level as we have committed to protecting your personal data. Where these
       countries or territories do not have personal data protection laws that are comparable to the
       laws applicable to our relationship with you, we will enter into legally enforceable agreements
       with the recipients.
Third Party Websites
24.    Our Applications may contain links to other websites that are not owned or maintained by us.
       These links are provided only for your convenience. This Privacy Policy only applies to our
       Applications. When visiting these third party websites, you should read their privacy policies.
Automatic Data Collection Technologies
25.    We use Automatic Data Collection Technologies on our Applications. Examples of such
       technologies include:
       25.1.    Cookies (or browser cookies). Cookies are small text files which are set by a
                website or application operator so that your browser or device may be recognized.
                We may make use of cookies on our Applications to store and track information such
                as the number of users and their frequency of use, profiles of users and their online
                preferences. Cookies do not capture information which would personally identify you,
                                  Privacy Policy || X-Block Foundation Ltd.

                 but the information collected may be used to assist us in analyzing the usage of our
                 Applications and to improve your online experience with us. You can disable the
                 cookies by changing the setting on your browser. However, this may affect the
                 functionality of the Applications.
        25.2.    Flash cookies. Certain features of our Applications may use local stored objects (or
                 Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation
                 to, from, and on our Applications. In contrast to normal cookies, these cookies are not
                 created and saved by the web browser but are governed by the Adobe Flash plug-in.
                 These can contain more information than normal cookies and cannot be deleted or
                 disabled via the browser; this is only possible using tools such as the Adobe Flash
                 Player website. You can also obtain more information about these cookies on their
                 website.
        25.3.    Third Party Use of Cookies and other Tracking Technologies. Some content or
                 applications on the Applications, including advertisements, are served by third parties,
                 including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers, and application
                 providers. These third parties m a y use cookies alone or in conjunction with w e b
                 beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use
                 our Applications. The information they collect may be associated with your personal
                 information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your
                 online activities over time and across different websites and other online services.
                 They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral)
                 advertising or other targeted content. We do not control these third parties' tracking
                 technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an
                 advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider
                 directly.
        25.4.    We b Tracking Beacons and tracking links. Web beacons (also known as pixel
                 tags and clean GIFs) involve graphics that are not apparent to the user. Tracking
                 links and/or similar technologies consist of a few lines of programming code and can
                 be embedded in our website or our (mobile) applications. In conjunction with cookies,
                 these are primarily used for statistical analysis purposes. This technology can also be
                 used for tracking traffic patterns on websites, as well as finding out if an e-mail has
                 been received and opened and to see if there has been any response.
        25.5.    Google Analytics. Web analytics is the term given to a method for collecting and
                 assessing the behavior of visitors to websites and mobile applications. This includes
                 the analysis of traffic patterns in order, for example, to determine the frequency of
                 visits to certain parts of a website or mobile application, or to find out what information
                 and services our visitors are most interested in. The web analytics services on our
                 Applications are provided by Google Analytics. If you do not allow Google Analytics to
                 collect and assess information about your behavior at our Applications, you can
                 install the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on.
        25.6.    Facebook Pixel. A Facebook pixel is a code that is placed on websites for the
                 purpose of tracking conversions from Facebook advertisements, optimize
                 advertisements based on collected data, build targeted audiences for future
                 advertisements and remarketing our products and/or services to qualified leads (i.e.
                 when you done something on our Applications). A Facebook pixel works by placing
                 and triggering cookies to track users as they interact with our Applications and our
                 Facebook advertisements.
Your rights
26.     Contact Data Protection Officer. If you wish to withdraw any consent you have given us at
        any time, or if you wish to correct or have access to your personal data held by us, or if you
        do not accept any amendment to this Privacy Policy, please contact our Data Protection
        Officer:
                                    Privacy Policy || X-Block Foundation Ltd.

    Email             :       contact@x-block.io
27. Fee for access. We may charge you a fee for responding to your request for access to your
    personal data held by us, or for information about the ways in which we have (or may have)
    used your personal data in the one-year period preceding your request. If a fee is to be
    charged, w e will inform you of the amount beforehand and respond to your request after
    payment is received. We will endeavor to respond to your request within thirty (30) days, and if
    that is not possible, we will inform you of the time by which we will respond to you.
28. Effect of withdrawal of consent. In many circumstances, w e need to use your personal
    data in order for us to provide you with products or services that you require. If you do not
    provide us with the required personal data, or if you withdraw your consent to our use and/or
    disclosure of your personal data for these purposes, it may not be possible for us to continue
    to serve you or provide you with the products and services that you require.
                              Privacy Policy || X-Block Foundation Ltd.
